convert4.me 2014-11-20

# Convert4.Me

Convert4.Me is commited to protect your privacy and will only use information collected about you in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and the European Directive on Privacy and Electronic Communications (2002/58/EC).

The information we collect

We may collect personal information about you which you give to us when you use our Services.The provision of the Services to you may also require us to store details of your transactions. We will periodically review your personal information to ensure that we do not keep it for longer than is necessary. 

Purposes for which we use information about you

We may use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * to enable you to access and use the Services; and/or
  * to personalise aspects of our overall service to you; and/or
  * to communicate with you; and/or
  * to process a transaction between you and a third party.

Passing on information about you

Please be aware that once you use our Services, you will be regarded as having given your consent to us disclosing your personal information to the following parties: 

  * third party providers whose products or services are listed on the results pages of the channels on our website, for the purposes of downloading software for you or comparing different products and services as requested by you; 
  * The regulatory/governing bodies for the purposes of compliance monitoring; 
  * other third parties either where necessary for those third parties to provide additional products or services requested by you or with your prior consent. 

Informing you of offers and services which may be of interest

We would like to keep you updated by phone, e-mail or text of other products and services which we feel you may benefit from. For example, we may e-mail you letting you know how you could save money by switching product and services. Wherever we capture your data you will be asked to confirm your acceptance of us using your data for these purposes. By providing your information when you use our site, you consent to us disclosing your personal information to the following parties: 

  * other companies in the Convert4.Me Group of companies; and
  * our trusted business partners, whose products and services may be useful to you. 

You can ask us either via email or our conatct page to stop passing your information to third parties for marketing purposes at any time, which we will do. Such a request may result in us ceasing to offer the Services to you. 

We may disclose information about you in connection with legal proceedings or potential legal proceedings or if otherwise permitted to do so by law. 

Electronic Communications

When you agree to receive any electronic communications from us, you also agree to receive additional communications on products and services which we believe you may be interested in. Any electronic communications we send you will include clear and concise instructions to follow should you wish to unsubscribe at any time. 

Third party providers and data privacy

If you decide to enter into a contract with a third party provider through a channel on our website, the information you have provided to us together with any further information requested by, and supplied by you to, the third party provider will be held by the provider for the purposes set out in that provider's privacy policy. Therefore, you are strongly advised to read your chosen provider's privacy policy and satisfy yourself as to the purposes for which the provider will use your personal information before entering into the contract. We have no responsibility for the uses to which a provider puts your personal information once you have contracted with that provider. 

Cookies

Cookies are a means by which information relating to your Internet activity (such as whether you have visited a website before) is recorded on your hard drive and used by us to improve the websites and the products and services available to you. If you do not wish for us to use cookies when you use this site please adjust your Internet browser settings to not accept cookies. Your computer’s help file should tell you how to do this. Alternatively visit www.dma.org.uk for information on how to do this.

Third party vendors, including Google, show your ads on sites on the internet.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.

Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page.
